[{"subjectID":"gfe304y3u9","prolificID":"675d6e70a2eedcd7ec6d674c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1e4e54abf6ee83ce3b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678957363,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"32","question":"Of all the people in your family, whose death would you find most tragic or difficult? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":23904,"timeElapsed":177006},{"subjectID":"gfe304y3u9","prolificID":"675d6e70a2eedcd7ec6d674c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1e4e54abf6ee83ce3b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678973085,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"32","question":"Of all the people in your family, whose death would you find most tragic or difficult? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":15719,"timeElapsed":192727},{"subjectID":"gfe304y3u9","prolificID":"675d6e70a2eedcd7ec6d674c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1e4e54abf6ee83ce3b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678996719,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"32","question":"Of all the people in your family, whose death would you find most tragic or difficult? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":34,"rt":23630,"timeElapsed":216362},{"subjectID":"gfe304y3u9","prolificID":"675d6e70a2eedcd7ec6d674c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1e4e54abf6ee83ce3b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679009772,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"32","question":"Of all the people in your family, whose death would you find most tragic or difficult? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":13049,"timeElapsed":229415},{"subjectID":"gfe304y3u9","prolificID":"675d6e70a2eedcd7ec6d674c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1e4e54abf6ee83ce3b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679018182,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"32","question":"Of all the people in your family, whose death would you find most tragic or difficult? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":8405,"timeElapsed":237825},{"subjectID":"gfe304y3u9","prolificID":"675d6e70a2eedcd7ec6d674c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1e4e54abf6ee83ce3b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679032895,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"32","question":"Of all the people in your family, whose death would you find most tragic or difficult? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":14709,"timeElapsed":252538},{"subjectID":"gfe304y3u9","prolificID":"675d6e70a2eedcd7ec6d674c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1e4e54abf6ee83ce3b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679039221,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"32","question":"Of all the people in your family, whose death would you find most tragic or difficult? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":6321,"timeElapsed":258864},{"subjectID":"gfe304y3u9","prolificID":"675d6e70a2eedcd7ec6d674c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1e4e54abf6ee83ce3b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679043705,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"32","question":"Of all the people in your family, whose death would you find most tragic or difficult? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":27,"rt":4481,"timeElapsed":263348},{"subjectID":"gfe304y3u9","prolificID":"675d6e70a2eedcd7ec6d674c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1e4e54abf6ee83ce3b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679047768,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"32","question":"Of all the people in your family, whose death would you find most tragic or difficult? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4060,"timeElapsed":267411},{"subjectID":"gfe304y3u9","prolificID":"675d6e70a2eedcd7ec6d674c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1e4e54abf6ee83ce3b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679064564,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"220","question":"If you had to live in a movie, book, or tv show universe (for example, the world of harry potter, twilight, dune or hunger games), which one would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":14640,"timeElapsed":284207},{"subjectID":"gfe304y3u9","prolificID":"675d6e70a2eedcd7ec6d674c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1e4e54abf6ee83ce3b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679070506,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"220","question":"If you had to live in a movie, book, or tv show universe (for example, the world of harry potter, twilight, dune or hunger games), which one would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":5937,"timeElapsed":290148},{"subjectID":"gfe304y3u9","prolificID":"675d6e70a2eedcd7ec6d674c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1e4e54abf6ee83ce3b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679077402,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"220","question":"If you had to live in a movie, book, or tv show universe (for example, the world of harry potter, twilight, dune or hunger games), which one would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":6892,"timeElapsed":297045},{"subjectID":"gfe304y3u9","prolificID":"675d6e70a2eedcd7ec6d674c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1e4e54abf6ee83ce3b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679084052,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"220","question":"If you had to live in a movie, book, or tv show universe (for example, the world of harry potter, twilight, dune or hunger games), which one would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":6645,"timeElapsed":303695},{"subjectID":"gfe304y3u9","prolificID":"675d6e70a2eedcd7ec6d674c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1e4e54abf6ee83ce3b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679091925,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"220","question":"If you had to live in a movie, book, or tv show universe (for example, the world of harry potter, twilight, dune or hunger games), which one would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":7869,"timeElapsed":311568},{"subjectID":"gfe304y3u9","prolificID":"675d6e70a2eedcd7ec6d674c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1e4e54abf6ee83ce3b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679098865,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"220","question":"If you had to live in a movie, book, or tv show universe (for example, the world of harry potter, twilight, dune or hunger games), which one would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":6936,"timeElapsed":318507},{"subjectID":"gfe304y3u9","prolificID":"675d6e70a2eedcd7ec6d674c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1e4e54abf6ee83ce3b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679103395,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"220","question":"If you had to live in a movie, book, or tv show universe (for example, the world of harry potter, twilight, dune or hunger games), which one would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":31,"rt":4526,"timeElapsed":323037},{"subjectID":"gfe304y3u9","prolificID":"675d6e70a2eedcd7ec6d674c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1e4e54abf6ee83ce3b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679108301,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"220","question":"If you had to live in a movie, book, or tv show universe (for example, the world of harry potter, twilight, dune or hunger games), which one would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":4902,"timeElapsed":327944},{"subjectID":"gfe304y3u9","prolificID":"675d6e70a2eedcd7ec6d674c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1e4e54abf6ee83ce3b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679112454,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"220","question":"If you had to live in a movie, book, or tv show universe (for example, the world of harry potter, twilight, dune or hunger games), which one would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":32,"rt":4149,"timeElapsed":332097},{"subjectID":"gfe304y3u9","prolificID":"675d6e70a2eedcd7ec6d674c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1e4e54abf6ee83ce3b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679183654,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"202","question":"Who was the last person you met up with outside your home or theirs? What did you do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":69243,"timeElapsed":403297},{"subjectID":"gfe304y3u9","prolificID":"675d6e70a2eedcd7ec6d674c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1e4e54abf6ee83ce3b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679190938,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"202","question":"Who was the last person you met up with outside your home or theirs? What did you do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":28,"rt":7280,"timeElapsed":410581},{"subjectID":"gfe304y3u9","prolificID":"675d6e70a2eedcd7ec6d674c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1e4e54abf6ee83ce3b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679195166,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"202","question":"Who was the last person you met up with outside your home or theirs? What did you do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":4225,"timeElapsed":414809},{"subjectID":"gfe304y3u9","prolificID":"675d6e70a2eedcd7ec6d674c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1e4e54abf6ee83ce3b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679198909,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"202","question":"Who was the last person you met up with outside your home or theirs? What did you do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":32,"rt":3739,"timeElapsed":418552},{"subjectID":"gfe304y3u9","prolificID":"675d6e70a2eedcd7ec6d674c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1e4e54abf6ee83ce3b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679202773,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"202","question":"Who was the last person you met up with outside your home or theirs? What did you do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":3860,"timeElapsed":422416},{"subjectID":"gfe304y3u9","prolificID":"675d6e70a2eedcd7ec6d674c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1e4e54abf6ee83ce3b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679209730,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"202","question":"Who was the last person you met up with outside your home or theirs? What did you do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":6954,"timeElapsed":429373},{"subjectID":"gfe304y3u9","prolificID":"675d6e70a2eedcd7ec6d674c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1e4e54abf6ee83ce3b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679215875,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"202","question":"Who was the last person you met up with outside your home or theirs? What did you do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":6142,"timeElapsed":435518},{"subjectID":"gfe304y3u9","prolificID":"675d6e70a2eedcd7ec6d674c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1e4e54abf6ee83ce3b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679219437,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"202","question":"Who was the last person you met up with outside your home or theirs? What did you do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":3558,"timeElapsed":439080},{"subjectID":"gfe304y3u9","prolificID":"675d6e70a2eedcd7ec6d674c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1e4e54abf6ee83ce3b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679222376,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"202","question":"Who was the last person you met up with outside your home or theirs? What did you do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":2936,"timeElapsed":442019},{"subjectID":"gfe304y3u9","prolificID":"675d6e70a2eedcd7ec6d674c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1e4e54abf6ee83ce3b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679232682,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"174","question":"Have you ever tried to cut your own hair? How did that work out?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":8512,"timeElapsed":452325},{"subjectID":"gfe304y3u9","prolificID":"675d6e70a2eedcd7ec6d674c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1e4e54abf6ee83ce3b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679237288,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"174","question":"Have you ever tried to cut your own hair? How did that work out?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":4602,"timeElapsed":456930},{"subjectID":"gfe304y3u9","prolificID":"675d6e70a2eedcd7ec6d674c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1e4e54abf6ee83ce3b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679245409,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"174","question":"Have you ever tried to cut your own hair? How did that work out?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":8119,"timeElapsed":465052},{"subjectID":"gfe304y3u9","prolificID":"675d6e70a2eedcd7ec6d674c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1e4e54abf6ee83ce3b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679252451,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"174","question":"Have you ever tried to cut your own hair? How did that work out?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":7039,"timeElapsed":472094},{"subjectID":"gfe304y3u9","prolificID":"675d6e70a2eedcd7ec6d674c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1e4e54abf6ee83ce3b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679255660,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"174","question":"Have you ever tried to cut your own hair? How did that work out?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":3205,"timeElapsed":475303},{"subjectID":"gfe304y3u9","prolificID":"675d6e70a2eedcd7ec6d674c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1e4e54abf6ee83ce3b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679287335,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"174","question":"Have you ever tried to cut your own hair? How did that work out?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":31672,"timeElapsed":506978},{"subjectID":"gfe304y3u9","prolificID":"675d6e70a2eedcd7ec6d674c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1e4e54abf6ee83ce3b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679294999,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"174","question":"Have you ever tried to cut your own hair? How did that work out?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":7660,"timeElapsed":514642},{"subjectID":"gfe304y3u9","prolificID":"675d6e70a2eedcd7ec6d674c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1e4e54abf6ee83ce3b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679300425,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"174","question":"Have you ever tried to cut your own hair? How did that work out?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":5423,"timeElapsed":520068},{"subjectID":"gfe304y3u9","prolificID":"675d6e70a2eedcd7ec6d674c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1e4e54abf6ee83ce3b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679366202,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"174","question":"Have you ever tried to cut your own hair? How did that work out?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":65773,"timeElapsed":585845},{"subjectID":"gfe304y3u9","prolificID":"675d6e70a2eedcd7ec6d674c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1e4e54abf6ee83ce3b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679408740,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":40129,"timeElapsed":628382},{"subjectID":"gfe304y3u9","prolificID":"675d6e70a2eedcd7ec6d674c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1e4e54abf6ee83ce3b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679418218,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":9475,"timeElapsed":637861},{"subjectID":"gfe304y3u9","prolificID":"675d6e70a2eedcd7ec6d674c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1e4e54abf6ee83ce3b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679422186,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":3964,"timeElapsed":641829},{"subjectID":"gfe304y3u9","prolificID":"675d6e70a2eedcd7ec6d674c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1e4e54abf6ee83ce3b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679428336,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":6146,"timeElapsed":647979},{"subjectID":"gfe304y3u9","prolificID":"675d6e70a2eedcd7ec6d674c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1e4e54abf6ee83ce3b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679434468,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":6127,"timeElapsed":654111},{"subjectID":"gfe304y3u9","prolificID":"675d6e70a2eedcd7ec6d674c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1e4e54abf6ee83ce3b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679437947,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":3475,"timeElapsed":657590},{"subjectID":"gfe304y3u9","prolificID":"675d6e70a2eedcd7ec6d674c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1e4e54abf6ee83ce3b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679442022,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":52,"rt":4071,"timeElapsed":661664},{"subjectID":"gfe304y3u9","prolificID":"675d6e70a2eedcd7ec6d674c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1e4e54abf6ee83ce3b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679445282,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":3257,"timeElapsed":664925},{"subjectID":"gfe304y3u9","prolificID":"675d6e70a2eedcd7ec6d674c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1e4e54abf6ee83ce3b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679460497,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":15211,"timeElapsed":680139},{"subjectID":"gfe304y3u9","prolificID":"675d6e70a2eedcd7ec6d674c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1e4e54abf6ee83ce3b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679464260,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":3760,"timeElapsed":683903},{"subjectID":"gfe304y3u9","prolificID":"675d6e70a2eedcd7ec6d674c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1e4e54abf6ee83ce3b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679576599,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"58","question":"If you had to give away all of your money tomorrow, what cause or causes would you want to support? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":109057,"timeElapsed":796242},{"subjectID":"gfe304y3u9","prolificID":"675d6e70a2eedcd7ec6d674c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1e4e54abf6ee83ce3b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679580155,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"58","question":"If you had to give away all of your money tomorrow, what cause or causes would you want to support? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":3553,"timeElapsed":799798},{"subjectID":"gfe304y3u9","prolificID":"675d6e70a2eedcd7ec6d674c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1e4e54abf6ee83ce3b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679582931,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"58","question":"If you had to give away all of your money tomorrow, what cause or causes would you want to support? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":2772,"timeElapsed":802574},{"subjectID":"gfe304y3u9","prolificID":"675d6e70a2eedcd7ec6d674c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1e4e54abf6ee83ce3b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679586795,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"58","question":"If you had to give away all of your money tomorrow, what cause or causes would you want to support? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":3860,"timeElapsed":806438},{"subjectID":"gfe304y3u9","prolificID":"675d6e70a2eedcd7ec6d674c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1e4e54abf6ee83ce3b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679589710,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"58","question":"If you had to give away all of your money tomorrow, what cause or causes would you want to support? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":2912,"timeElapsed":809353},{"subjectID":"gfe304y3u9","prolificID":"675d6e70a2eedcd7ec6d674c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1e4e54abf6ee83ce3b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679592797,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"58","question":"If you had to give away all of your money tomorrow, what cause or causes would you want to support? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":3083,"timeElapsed":812440},{"subjectID":"gfe304y3u9","prolificID":"675d6e70a2eedcd7ec6d674c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1e4e54abf6ee83ce3b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679596228,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"58","question":"If you had to give away all of your money tomorrow, what cause or causes would you want to support? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":3427,"timeElapsed":815871},{"subjectID":"gfe304y3u9","prolificID":"675d6e70a2eedcd7ec6d674c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1e4e54abf6ee83ce3b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679600714,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"58","question":"If you had to give away all of your money tomorrow, what cause or causes would you want to support? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":4482,"timeElapsed":820356},{"subjectID":"gfe304y3u9","prolificID":"675d6e70a2eedcd7ec6d674c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1e4e54abf6ee83ce3b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679606018,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"58","question":"If you had to give away all of your money tomorrow, what cause or causes would you want to support? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":5302,"timeElapsed":825661},{"subjectID":"gfe304y3u9","prolificID":"675d6e70a2eedcd7ec6d674c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1e4e54abf6ee83ce3b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679615151,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":7337,"timeElapsed":834794},{"subjectID":"gfe304y3u9","prolificID":"675d6e70a2eedcd7ec6d674c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1e4e54abf6ee83ce3b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679617912,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":2758,"timeElapsed":837555},{"subjectID":"gfe304y3u9","prolificID":"675d6e70a2eedcd7ec6d674c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1e4e54abf6ee83ce3b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679621362,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":3447,"timeElapsed":841005},{"subjectID":"gfe304y3u9","prolificID":"675d6e70a2eedcd7ec6d674c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1e4e54abf6ee83ce3b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679624183,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":2818,"timeElapsed":843826},{"subjectID":"gfe304y3u9","prolificID":"675d6e70a2eedcd7ec6d674c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1e4e54abf6ee83ce3b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679626954,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":2767,"timeElapsed":846597},{"subjectID":"gfe304y3u9","prolificID":"675d6e70a2eedcd7ec6d674c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1e4e54abf6ee83ce3b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679630505,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":3548,"timeElapsed":850148},{"subjectID":"gfe304y3u9","prolificID":"675d6e70a2eedcd7ec6d674c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1e4e54abf6ee83ce3b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679634001,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":3493,"timeElapsed":853644},{"subjectID":"gfe304y3u9","prolificID":"675d6e70a2eedcd7ec6d674c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1e4e54abf6ee83ce3b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679637984,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":3979,"timeElapsed":857627},{"subjectID":"gfe304y3u9","prolificID":"675d6e70a2eedcd7ec6d674c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1e4e54abf6ee83ce3b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679641156,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":3168,"timeElapsed":860799},{"subjectID":"gfe304y3u9","prolificID":"675d6e70a2eedcd7ec6d674c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1e4e54abf6ee83ce3b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679660951,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"41","question":"If you were given the chance to relive any day in your life, do you know which day it would be? What happened?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":18403,"timeElapsed":880593},{"subjectID":"gfe304y3u9","prolificID":"675d6e70a2eedcd7ec6d674c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1e4e54abf6ee83ce3b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679663595,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"41","question":"If you were given the chance to relive any day in your life, do you know which day it would be? What happened?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":2641,"timeElapsed":883238},{"subjectID":"gfe304y3u9","prolificID":"675d6e70a2eedcd7ec6d674c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1e4e54abf6ee83ce3b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679666295,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"41","question":"If you were given the chance to relive any day in your life, do you know which day it would be? What happened?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":2696,"timeElapsed":885938},{"subjectID":"gfe304y3u9","prolificID":"675d6e70a2eedcd7ec6d674c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1e4e54abf6ee83ce3b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679669465,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"41","question":"If you were given the chance to relive any day in your life, do you know which day it would be? What happened?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":3166,"timeElapsed":889108},{"subjectID":"gfe304y3u9","prolificID":"675d6e70a2eedcd7ec6d674c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1e4e54abf6ee83ce3b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679672803,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"41","question":"If you were given the chance to relive any day in your life, do you know which day it would be? What happened?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":3335,"timeElapsed":892446},{"subjectID":"gfe304y3u9","prolificID":"675d6e70a2eedcd7ec6d674c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1e4e54abf6ee83ce3b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679676099,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"41","question":"If you were given the chance to relive any day in your life, do you know which day it would be? What happened?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":3293,"timeElapsed":895742},{"subjectID":"gfe304y3u9","prolificID":"675d6e70a2eedcd7ec6d674c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1e4e54abf6ee83ce3b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679679420,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"41","question":"If you were given the chance to relive any day in your life, do you know which day it would be? What happened?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":3318,"timeElapsed":899063},{"subjectID":"gfe304y3u9","prolificID":"675d6e70a2eedcd7ec6d674c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1e4e54abf6ee83ce3b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679682010,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"41","question":"If you were given the chance to relive any day in your life, do you know which day it would be? What happened?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":2586,"timeElapsed":901653},{"subjectID":"gfe304y3u9","prolificID":"675d6e70a2eedcd7ec6d674c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1e4e54abf6ee83ce3b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679685162,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"41","question":"If you were given the chance to relive any day in your life, do you know which day it would be? What happened?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":3148,"timeElapsed":904805},{"subjectID":"gfe304y3u9","prolificID":"675d6e70a2eedcd7ec6d674c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1e4e54abf6ee83ce3b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679691179,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"If you were given the chance to relive any day in your life, do you know which day it would be? What happened?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":6014,"timeElapsed":910822},{"subjectID":"gfe304y3u9","prolificID":"675d6e70a2eedcd7ec6d674c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1e4e54abf6ee83ce3b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679699646,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"9","question":"For what in your life do you feel most grateful?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":6671,"timeElapsed":919289},{"subjectID":"gfe304y3u9","prolificID":"675d6e70a2eedcd7ec6d674c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1e4e54abf6ee83ce3b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679702614,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"9","question":"For what in your life do you feel most grateful?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":2965,"timeElapsed":922257},{"subjectID":"gfe304y3u9","prolificID":"675d6e70a2eedcd7ec6d674c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1e4e54abf6ee83ce3b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679705457,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"9","question":"For what in your life do you feel most grateful?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":2840,"timeElapsed":925100},{"subjectID":"gfe304y3u9","prolificID":"675d6e70a2eedcd7ec6d674c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1e4e54abf6ee83ce3b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679708617,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"9","question":"For what in your life do you feel most grateful?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":3156,"timeElapsed":928260},{"subjectID":"gfe304y3u9","prolificID":"675d6e70a2eedcd7ec6d674c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1e4e54abf6ee83ce3b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679711696,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"9","question":"For what in your life do you feel most grateful?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":3075,"timeElapsed":931339},{"subjectID":"gfe304y3u9","prolificID":"675d6e70a2eedcd7ec6d674c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1e4e54abf6ee83ce3b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679720680,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"9","question":"For what in your life do you feel most grateful?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":8980,"timeElapsed":940322},{"subjectID":"gfe304y3u9","prolificID":"675d6e70a2eedcd7ec6d674c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1e4e54abf6ee83ce3b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679724108,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"9","question":"For what in your life do you feel most grateful?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":3425,"timeElapsed":943751},{"subjectID":"gfe304y3u9","prolificID":"675d6e70a2eedcd7ec6d674c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1e4e54abf6ee83ce3b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679727058,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"9","question":"For what in your life do you feel most grateful?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":2946,"timeElapsed":946701},{"subjectID":"gfe304y3u9","prolificID":"675d6e70a2eedcd7ec6d674c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1e4e54abf6ee83ce3b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679730175,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"9","question":"For what in your life do you feel most grateful?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":3114,"timeElapsed":949818},{"subjectID":"gfe304y3u9","prolificID":"675d6e70a2eedcd7ec6d674c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1e4e54abf6ee83ce3b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679738822,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"40","question":"If you could visit your past self at a younger age and offer your past self advice about how to live your life (not just where to invest your money…), what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":6940,"timeElapsed":958464},{"subjectID":"gfe304y3u9","prolificID":"675d6e70a2eedcd7ec6d674c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1e4e54abf6ee83ce3b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679742386,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"40","question":"If you could visit your past self at a younger age and offer your past self advice about how to live your life (not just where to invest your money…), what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":3561,"timeElapsed":962029},{"subjectID":"gfe304y3u9","prolificID":"675d6e70a2eedcd7ec6d674c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1e4e54abf6ee83ce3b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679749973,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"40","question":"If you could visit your past self at a younger age and offer your past self advice about how to live your life (not just where to invest your money…), what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":29,"rt":7584,"timeElapsed":969616},{"subjectID":"gfe304y3u9","prolificID":"675d6e70a2eedcd7ec6d674c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1e4e54abf6ee83ce3b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679753887,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"40","question":"If you could visit your past self at a younger age and offer your past self advice about how to live your life (not just where to invest your money…), what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":3911,"timeElapsed":973530},{"subjectID":"gfe304y3u9","prolificID":"675d6e70a2eedcd7ec6d674c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1e4e54abf6ee83ce3b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679757752,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"40","question":"If you could visit your past self at a younger age and offer your past self advice about how to live your life (not just where to invest your money…), what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":3861,"timeElapsed":977395},{"subjectID":"gfe304y3u9","prolificID":"675d6e70a2eedcd7ec6d674c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1e4e54abf6ee83ce3b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679761695,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"40","question":"If you could visit your past self at a younger age and offer your past self advice about how to live your life (not just where to invest your money…), what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":3939,"timeElapsed":981338},{"subjectID":"gfe304y3u9","prolificID":"675d6e70a2eedcd7ec6d674c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1e4e54abf6ee83ce3b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679765282,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"40","question":"If you could visit your past self at a younger age and offer your past self advice about how to live your life (not just where to invest your money…), what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":3583,"timeElapsed":984925},{"subjectID":"gfe304y3u9","prolificID":"675d6e70a2eedcd7ec6d674c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1e4e54abf6ee83ce3b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679768945,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"40","question":"If you could visit your past self at a younger age and offer your past self advice about how to live your life (not just where to invest your money…), what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":3662,"timeElapsed":988588},{"subjectID":"gfe304y3u9","prolificID":"675d6e70a2eedcd7ec6d674c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1e4e54abf6ee83ce3b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679772968,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"40","question":"If you could visit your past self at a younger age and offer your past self advice about how to live your life (not just where to invest your money…), what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":4018,"timeElapsed":992610}]